<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Robert Marck</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Robert Marck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 22:34:36 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm for Generating a Memorable and Secure Password</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/working_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 22:34:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/working_notes/</guid>
      <description>This is based loosely on the algorithm from XKCD: https://xkcd.com/936/, and a conversation with a friend. He told me his password and I still remember it, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use it to get into his information.
The goal is to make a pasword that is 1. Hard to crack, and 2. Easy to remember
Pick a comic/movie/song/painting/poem/book that is meaningful to you. The more meaningful the better, but don&amp;rsquo;t pick your favorite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cissp Notes Day 1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/cissp_notes_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 11:48:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/cissp_notes_1/</guid>
      <description>Done:
Got into the gym last night. &amp;ndash; A bunch (9?) sled pulls backwards and forwards. Working on correcting my knee issues. 135 lbs. &amp;ndash; Leg/knee lifts. Good for the Iliopsoas. Gonna keep doing these. &amp;ndash; Deadhangs: Made a huge difference in my should comfort. Gotta keep doing them. &amp;ndash; API Tests for the Console endpoints started. &amp;ndash; Docker Tutorial started. To Do:
Image support on my site is not working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second_post</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/second_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:22:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/second_post/</guid>
      <description>Website Done:
Installed Hugo on personal computer Set up access on work machine for monitoring Set up Amplify, and completed a successful build Site published! Banner photo added and working on local To Do:
Add photos to posts Integrate LaTeX Get banner working on live site Workout
Back in the gym last night. Goal was to just get in the door. Once that was done everything else was a bonus. I focuses on rehab movements: sled pulls, reverse sled pulls, dead hangs, and leg lifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 23:43:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post. I&amp;rsquo;m probably on iteration 16 or something getting hugo set up.
My next goal is to get LaTeX running for my editor.
That and start documenting my learning process.
Glad to be done with this though.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
